But an application can require prompting an LLM multiple times and parsing its output.
但是一个应用程序可能需要多次对
大语言模型写提示并对它输出的结果进行解析。
And so there's a lot of glue code that needs to be written.
因此，需要编写很多胶水代码。
LangChain created by Harrison Chase makes this development process much easier.
Harrison Chase创建的LangChain
使这个开发过程变得更容易。
I'm thrilled to have Harrison here, who had built this short course in collaboration with deeplearning.ai to teach how to use this amazing tool.
我很高兴邀请到Harrison，他与deeplearning.ai
合作创建了这个短期课程，教大家如何使用这个神奇的工具。
Thanks for having me. I'm really excited to be here.
谢谢Andrew的邀请，我很高兴来到这里。
LangChain started as an open source framework for building LLM applications.
LangChain起初是一个用于构建
大语言模型应用的开源框架。
It came about when I was talking to a bunch of folks in the field who were building more complex applications and saw some common abstractions in terms of how they were being developed.
当时有些人在开发LLM的复杂应用，当我与他们交流时，
发现了可以从中有一些公共的抽象，于是LangChain应运而生。
And we've been really thrilled at the community adoption of LangChain so far.
迄今为止，LangChain在社区中
的采用情况非常令人激动。
And so look forward to sharing it with everyone here and look forward to seeing what people build with it.
期待与大家分享，也期待看到
大家用它做出精彩的作品。
And in fact, as a sign of LangChain's momentum, not only does it have numerous users, but there are also many hundreds of contributors to the open source.
事实上，从一个现象你就可以看到LangChain的良好发展势头：
它不仅拥有众多用户，还有数百名贡献者为其开源项目做出了贡献。
And this has been instrumental for its rapid rate of development.
这对于它的快速发展至关重要。
This team really ships code and features at an amazing pace.
这个团队更新代码和迭代
功能的速度令人惊叹。
So hopefully, after this short course, you'll be able to quickly put together some really cool applications using LangChain.
希望在学习完这个短期课程后，你
也能迅速用LangChain搭建出很酷的应用。
And who knows, maybe you even decide to contribute back to the open source LangChain effort.
说不定你还能一起参与贡
献LangChain开源项目。
LangChain is an open source development framework for building LLM applications.
LangChain是一个用于构建
LLM应用的开源开发框架。
We have two different packages, a Python one and a JavaScript(TypeScript) one.
我们有两个不同的包，一个是Python，
另一个是JavaScript（TypeScript）。
They're focused on composition and modularity.
LangChain注重组合和模块化。
So they have a lot of individual components that can be used in conjunction with each other or by themselves.
LangChain一个很有价值的地方是有很多
可以单独使用或与其他组件结合使用的独立组件。
So chains of ways of combining these modular components into more end-to-end applications and making it very easy to get started with those use cases.
可以将这些模块化组件链式组合成更完
整的应用程序，并且非常容易上手。
In this class, we'll cover the common components of LangChain.
在这个课程中，我们将介绍
LangChain的常见组件。
We'll talk about prompts, which are how you get models to do useful and interesting things.
我们会讨论提示，这是让模型
做有用和有趣事情的方法。
And then we'll talk about chains,
然后我们会讨论链式应用，更
多端到端的用例以及代理，
which are a very exciting type of end-to-end use case,
代理一种非常令人兴奋的端到端用例
，使用大语言模型作为推理引擎。
We're also grateful to Ankush Gola,
我们也感谢Ankush Gola，
who is the co-founder of LangChain alongside Harrison Chase,
他与Harrison Chase共
同创立了LangChain，
for also putting a lot of thoughts into these materials and helping with the creation of this short course.
他在这些材料的思考和短课程的
创建中也做出了很大的贡献。
And on the deep learning, the AI side, Geoff Ladwig, Eddie Shyu, and Diala Ezzedine have also contributed to these materials.
在深度学习和AI方面，Geoff Ladwig、
Eddie Shyu和Diala Ezzedine也为这些材料做出了贡献。
And so with that, let's go on to the next video where we'll learn about LangChain's: Models, Prompts, and Parsers.
那么，让我们继续下一个视频，
了解LangChain的：模型、提示和解析器。